We are waiting for you. Please be careful.
Why did you say you were coming!
Hello. I am Director Hoshi of the Village of Ukka.
Today is April 1.
April 1st, the Osaka stop of the Spring Tour.
Today's person in charge is Director Murahoshi. I'll be sending you a message.
Well then, here you go!
This is Nakane Sora from Vegetable Stick.
He is eating vegetable sticks.
He's eating them. It's a little shiny.
Oh, I'm home.
You are in Osaka today, aren't you?
Enjoy your elegant meal.
Warm up your body and soul with miso soup.
Pokka pokka.
Pokka pokka!
It's no good. The line isn't over.
I'm not eating today.
I'll go with this.
With this?
Yes, sir.
And the lunch?
The bento,
I ordered today.
551.
551, I knew you would say Osaka!
Me too, 551.
I mean, you are all of you, aren't you?
Yakisoba?
Something with beef.
Yakisoba and
and shumai (steamed pork dumplings).
I chose shumai.
Both of them.
And for the chick with the hair.
Okay, from the shumai.
I washed my hands.
I'll start with the shumai.
If I eat it even now, it's too rehearsed
Bon appétit!
Mmmm...
Oh, it's open.
It's delicious, but...
I didn't draw my eyebrows.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A little bit on my hand.
I'm still in the process of making up.
I'm...
Glowing... glowing... glowing... glowing...
Fried rice.
Here you go, fried rice.
What's fried rice?
How's it look?
I knew it.
One o'clock in the afternoon is the best time.
It's great.
Okay, I'll go to rehearsal.
Let's do it.
Rehearsal is over.
Oh, Pia's make-up is on.
It looks good, but the lame on this side doesn't shine so much.
Glitter.
Oh, nice.
Very nice.
Today's eyeshadow
Glitter.
Is.
It's...
Looks good.
Good bye.
It begins. Finally, the Osaka show will begin.
You know, I was born in Osaka,
Tea.
Since the show is in Osaka, I would like to enjoy it.
Please enjoy the show.
Okay, everyone. This is the last performance of the first report.
All right, let's have fun.
Today's show is sold out.
Congratulations.Congratulations.
Thank you.
Well, let's do our best.
Aimeen, Ryu, Sora, Ruri, Mo, Mo, Lian, Uka, Fai!
Please.
Let's go this way.
I'll go here.
Thank you very much.
I'm going.
Welcome!
Leave it yesterday and take it to the sky.
From this far away.
Even running out is perfect.
It's so pleasurable
That scorching new star
Is born now.
Two.
Mmm.
Good candy.
Yes, sir.
ran
Ollintober Black sky is blue because
Ollintober. Ollintober.
Is it for you?
Ollintober, Ollintober
The black sky is blue because of you
Ollintober, Ollintober, Ollintober
Is it for your sake?
Ollintober, Ollintober
I just like what I like to do
I'm trying so hard to prove my existence
Communication is in full swing
Likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes likes
Like like like like like communion communion
I'm not alone
You're your own winner
Aurintobar Aurintobar
Thank you for watching!
It's over! Thank you very much!
It's hot! Hot! Hot!
Thank you for your hard work!
It was fun, the Osaka show!
My hometown...
Can I say "local"?
It was fun. Thank you very much!